

0431 808 027

angela\_rodmo@hotmail.com

76 Wallbank Way, Bulli NSW

I am a passionate multidisciplinary web front-end developer and designer with the ability to seamlessly blend my design and front-end technical experience. I have worked in different interactive projects involving the design, build and maintenance of websites for various brands as well as using a wide range of web tools and technologies.

## Skills Set

Strong visual and creative skills

Natural design sense (layout, typography, colour, etc.)

Responsive design techniques

HTML/CSS - Extensive experience

JavaScript/JQuery - Practical experience

Browser Testing/Troubleshooting

Accessibility guidelines (W3C)

SEO - Best practices knowledge

## Software

Adobe CC (XD, Photoshop and Illustrator)
Exposure to Figma and InVision
Webflow
WordPress/Drupal/Alfresco
Confluence/Trello
JIRA - Issue & Project Tracking Software
MS Word, MS Excel and MS PowerPoint
Operating Systems: Mac and Windows

# Employment

Front End Web Developer/Designer nextmedia Pty Ltd, Sydney

Sep 2016 - Current

- Creating wireframes and mock-ups for websites and digital products
- Designing and implementing websites, microsites, landing pages and eDM templates
- Integrating front-end design into PHP and .Net websites
- Executing front-end web development tasks and projects using HTML and CSS
- Implementating web concepts and designs using Bootstrap
- Implementing responsive design and development to websites
- · Liaising with key stakeholders in relation to the choices of web design
- Collaborating with the sales, marketing, production and digital teams on the look and feel and delivery of websites and digital products for B2B and consumer brands
- Using debugging tools and website tracking tools such as Google Tag Manager, Google Search Console, Google Analytics and Hotjar
- Creating end user documentation

## **Employment**

#### Freelance Web Designer/Developer WebBuzz, DT Digital, EM Creative & Small Businesses, Sydney

Jan 2015 - Sep 2016

- · Created web images, graphic elements and layouts
- · Designed eDMs, landing pages and digital assets
- · Coded with HTML and CSS
- Customised and implemented WordPress themes
- · Updated, maintained and tested clients websites
- · Created social media profiles and assets

#### Digital Producer/Designer HotHouse Interactive, Sydney

Jan 2014 - Jan 2015

- Created and designed assets for web and mobile (layouts, graphics, banners, etc.)
- Designed internal marketing
- Supported the creative/UX design team
- · Coded HTML pages for website and mobile and updated website content through GIT
- Edited, optimised and uploaded images and videos
- Performed content testing and site quality maintenance over multiple browsers and devices
- Participated in project meetings and worked closely with project managers and different teams

# Freelance Web Designer Illegal Design & Small Businesses, Sydney

Sept 2012 - Dec 2013

- · Created web images, graphic elements, layouts and digital assets
- Planned, designed and implemented complete web sites
- · Coded with HTML, CSS and basic PHP
- Updated and maintained clients websites
- Tested and debugged websites for usability and accessibility
- Discussed website requirements with clients

## **Employment**

#### Web Designer/Marketing Coordinator Aroma Coffee Roastery Pty, Marrickville

Nov 2009 - Aug 2012

- · Planned, designed and implemented company's website
- · Created web animations, layouts and graphic elements
- · Coordinated updates and continual maintenance of the company's website
- Designed and organised printing of collaterals (promotion flyers, business cards, etc.)
- · Created and managed Google ad campaigns
- · Updated the products and promotions of the online product catalogue
- · Coordinated monthly email communications to customers
- Designed user interface of company's Iphone application
- · Worked cooperatively with team members and clients

#### Admin Support/ Customer service Aroma Coffee Roastery Pty, Marrickville

May 2007 - Nov 2009

- · Organised & prepared documents, reports & formal letters
- Provided administrative support to general manager
- · Responded to customer enquiries both written and over the phone
- Dealt with customer complaints

# E- learning Assistant (Work Experience) IBM, Sydney

April 2006

- Updated online content
- · Assisted in creation of E-learning applications
- Assisted with HTML and CSS implementation

## Education

Bachelor of Information Systems Australian Catholic University, North Sydney	2007
Responsive Web Design (WordPress) General Assembly, Sydney	2014
Diploma of Web Design and Development TAFE, Ultimo	2010
Diploma of Information Technology (Multimedia Integration) Windsor Institute, Sydney	2005

## Additional Skills and Abilities

Excellent attention to detail

Ability to work as part of a team and autonomously

Excellent communication skills (written and verbal)

Time management skills

Hard working and committed

Both creative and technical aptitude

Flexible and adaptable with competent interpersonal skills

Goal focused and motivated to exceed expectations

Customer focus

### Interests

Bush walking, theatre, dancing and technology

## References

Available upon request